Finding Aid for the Mary Ella Calhoun Foote Estate Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Mary Ella Calhoun Foote Estate Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0149
.84 linear feet
- Correspondence
  - 1860 and 1880 (Box 1, Folder File 1)
  - 1881 (Box 1, Folder File 2)
  - 1882 (Box 1, Folder File 3)
  - 1883- 1889 (Box 1, Folder File 4)
  - 1890- 1894 (Box 1, Folder File 5)
  - 1895, 1899, 1902 (Box 1, Folder File 6)
  - 1903-1905 (Box 1, Folder File 7)
  - 1907-1914 (Box 1, Folder File 8)
  - February 1918 (Box 1, Folder File 9)
  - March 1918 (Box 1, Folder File 10)
  - April- May 1918 (Box 1, Folder File 11)
  - June, August 1918 (Box 1, Folder File 12)
  - September- October 1918 (Box 1, Folder File 13)
  - November- December 1918 (Box 1, Folder File 14)
  - January- February 1919 (Box 1, Folder File 15)
  - March- May 1919 (Box 1, Folder File 16)
  - June- August 1919 (Box 1, Folder File 17)
  - September- December 1919 (Box 1, Folder File 18)
  - January 1920 (Box 1, Folder File 19)
  - February 1920 (Box 1, Folder File 20)
  - March 1920 (Box 1, Folder File 21)
  - April 1920 (Box 1, Folder File 22)
  - May 1923 (Box 1, Folder File 23)
  - June 1894 (Box 1, Folder File 24)
  - July- December 1920 (Box 1, Folder File 25)
  - January- March 1921 (Box 1, Folder File 26)
  - April 1921 (Box 1, Folder File 27)
  - May- June 1921 (Box 1, Folder File 28)
  - July- December 1921 (Box 1, Folder File 29)
  - 1922 (Box 1, Folder File 30)
  - January- February 1923 (Box 1, Folder File 31)
  - March 1923 (Box 1, Folder File 32)
  - April- June 1923 (Box 1, Folder File 33)
  - July- December 1923 (Box 1, Folder File 34)
  - January- February 1924 (Box 1, Folder File 35)
  - March 1924 (Box 1, Folder File 36)
  - April- May 1924 (Box 1, Folder File 37)
  - June 1924 (Box 1, Folder File 38)
  - July, September 1924 (Box 1, Folder File 39)
  - 1925- 1929 (Box 1, Folder File 40)
- Estate Papers
  - Nashville Real Estate-Deeds, 1844-1854 (Box 2, Folder File 1)
  - Nashville Real Estate- Deeds, 1844-1854 (Box 2, Folder File 1)
  - Nashville Real Estate- Deeds, 1856-1912 (Box 2, Folder File 2)
  - Nashville Real Estate- Survey, Map, Bills, Insurance, Correspondence, and Miscellaneous Materials (Box 2, Folder File 3)
  - Nashville Real Estate- Leases- Public Square, Fifth Avenue, and South Nashville (Box 2, Folder File 4)
  - Nashville Real Estate- Mount Olivet Cemetery (Box 2, Folder File 5)
  - New York Real Estate- Deeds, Mortgages, Insurance and Leases, 1889-1913 (Box 2, Folder File 6)
  - New York Real Estate- Deeds, Mortgages, Insurances and Leases 1918-1922 and Miscellaneous Materials (Box 2, Folder File 7)
  - New York Real Estate- Receipts, Bills, and Work Orders related to Leases of 113 West 13th Street (Box 2, Folder File 8)
  - North Carolina Real Estate- Deeds, Land Descriptions and Related Materials (Box 2, Folder File 9)
  - Real Estate- Taxes 1879-1923 (Tennessee, New York and North Carolina) (Box 2, Folder File 10)
  - Real Estate- Bills, 1876-1889 (Box 2, Folder File 11)
  - Estate Papers- Bank Account for Estate of Mary Ella Calhoun Foote- Account Statement and Cancelled Checks- New York (Box 2, Folder File 12)
  - Estate Papers- Bank Account for Estate of Mary Ella Calhoun Foote- Account Statement and Cancelled Checks – Nashville (Box 2, Folder File 13)
  - Estate Papers- Will of Mary Ella Calhoun Foote, and Related Papers (Box 2, Folder File 14)
  - Estate Papers- Appraisal of Estate (Box 2, Folder File 15)
  - Estate Papers-Lawsuit Statements (1919-1924) (Box 2, Folder File 16)
  - Estate Papers- Lawsuit against J. S. Glenn (Box 2, Folder File 17)
  - Estate Papers- Statements of the Estate (Box 2, Folder File 18)
  - Estate Papers- General Accounting and Miscellaneous Materials (Box 2, Folder File 19)
  - Estate Papers- Correspondence about Andrew Jackson Silver Service on Loan to the Hermitage (Box 2, Folder File 20)
  - Estate Papers- Ledger Book belonging to William H.enry Calhoun describing his personal property and real estate (Box 2, Folder File 21)
  - Miniatures of Mr. And Mrs. Foote (Box 2, Folder File 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder File 23)